

SHRADDHA TIWARI

+91 7381927536

tiwarishraddha82@gmail.co

m Elita F, cassa bella gold Pallava city , Mumbai , Maharastra

EDUCATION

 Bachelor of Business Administration KIIT School Of Management, Bhubaneswar (2016-2019)

Master's in Economics

Birla Global University, Bhubaneswar (2020-2022)

- Mount Carmel School, Rourkela 12th, Commerce
- St. Mary's School Rourkela 10th, Commerce

EXPERTISE

- Client Handling
- B2C Service
- Social Media Handling
- Marketing StrategiesLeadership Skills
- Communication Skills

ABOUT ME

Highly- motivated sales professional with 2+years of expertise in marketing strategic, client servicing, customer handling, social media handling and category supervision across diverse sector, A team leader with consistent record of converting sales prospect into loyal satisfied client and building a network of referrals to increase sales.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fanatisch Digital Marketing service, Mumbai

Sales team Leader 11/2022-11/2023

- Led staff meetings to delegate tasks, assign workloads and communicate changing priorities .Inspired and managed teams in operational improvements, increasing overall productivity.
- Managed operations efficiently and effectively, verifying customers received exceptional service.
- Inspired and managed teams in operational improvements, increasing overall productivity.
- Monitored team performance, providing suggestions for improvement and training programes to increase team efficiency Managed and mentored team of 5 to deliver exceptional service.

The Queen's English

Senior Business Development Executive 02/2022 - 10/2022

- Answered customers' questions regarding products, prices and availability.
- Increased monthly sales by implementing customer acquisition strategies Exceeded targeted sales goals through proactive outreach
- Cold and warm called new and existing accounts per day.

Lido Learning

Business Development Executive 03/2021 - 01/2022

- Developed business growth plans by identifying key clients, critical targets and priority service lines,
- Increased monthly sales by implementing customer acquisition strategies cold and warm called new and existing accounts per day.

LANGUAGE

English Hindi oriya French